question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The proof for the Chinese Remainder Theorem used in Number Theory was NOT developed by its first publisher, Sun Tzu.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "If you could fold a piece of paper in half 50 times, its&#039; thickness will be 3/4th the distance from the Earth to the Sun.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "E = MC3",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Zero factorial is equal to zero. ",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "You can square root a negative number with an imaginary number &quot;i&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "An equilateral triangle always has every angle measuring 60&deg;.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]
}

